<?xml version="1.0"?>
<locations>
    <locs>
        <locId>1</locId>
        <locCity>Minneapolis</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Red, White and BOOM celebrates Independence Day with music, entertainment and family fun on the Minneapolis Riverfront on July 3 and 4. Fireworks are at 10 p.m. on July 4. (NOTE: Powderhorn Park, Minneapolis will still host a Fourth of July celebration — with live music, children’s activities, and local food vendors — but will NOT feature a fireworks display this year.)</description>
        <locLocation>221 SE Main St Minneapolis, MN </locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>2</locId>
        <locCity>Albert Lea</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>On July 3, come see the largest parade in Southern Minnesota at 6 p.m. The parade has over 100 units and will travel Bridge and Fountain Streets.
            July 4 is one of the largest fireworks display in Southern Minnesota and Northern Iowa. Watch the beautiful reflection off of Fountain Lake at 10 p.m..
            Prior to the fireworks, the 4th Of July celebration will include:
            Community Band concert at 8 p.m. at the Gazebo.
            Bayside Ski Show at 2 p.m. at Edgewater Park.
            Car Show from 4 – 7 p.m. on N. Broadway.</description>
        <locLocation>Albert Lea, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>3</locId>
        <locCity>Alexandria</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Enjoy a free concert on the courthouse lawn beginning at 7 p.m. Friday, July 4. The concert is presented by the Red Willow Arts Coalition and will have a patriotic theme.
            Star Storm 2014 is a music and fireworks spectacular that is presented each year on the grounds of Arrowwood Resort. Tune your radio to KX92 – 92.3 FM to hear a patriotic sound track to the
            largest fireworks show in West Central Minnesota. It’s FREE and open to the public. Rainbow Rider shuttles will be running from the stables beginning at 7 p.m., fireworks begin at 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Alexandria, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>4</locId>
        <locCity>Andover</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description> July 3rd — Fireworks at AHS, at dusk
            July 4th — Family Fun in The Park:
            Pancake Breakfast — 8 – 11 am
            Jazz Band — 8 – 10 am
            Horribles Parade line-up — 9 am
            Horribles Parade — 9:30 am
            Games in The Park — 10 – 11:30 am
            Middlesex Concert Band — 10:30 – noon</description>
        <locLocation>Andover, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>5</locId>
        <locCity>Blaine</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description> What’s an Independence Day celebration
            without fireworks? Have your cameras ready and be
            prepared to be amazed by a fireworks display like no
            other Firework Extravaganza on July 4th at 10 p.m. at
            the National Sports Center</description>
        <locLocation>1700 150th Ave NE Blaine, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>6</locId>
        <locCity>Bloomington</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Summer Fete on July 3 celebrates Independence Day with a kid’s carnival, entertainment and live music.
            Fireworks will begin around 10 p.m. at Normandale Lake Bandshell.</description>
        <locLocation> Lake Bandshell Bloomington, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>7</locId>
        <locCity>Brainard</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>July 3rd
            5 p.m. Trampoline Bungee jumps, dunk tanks and food vendors
            5 – 8 p.m. Petting Zoo by Safari North Wildlife Park
            8 – 10 p.m. Music performance by Taylor Reed
            Fireworks, presented by Zambelli Fireworks, begin after dusk at the International-High School Ball Fields.
            July 4
            9 a.m.-4 p.m. Flea Market, Craft Fair and Food Vendors – Trailside Park
            10 a.m. Money in the Haystack-Trailside Park
            10:30 a.m. Kiddie Parade Registration-Chamber Building Parking Lot
            11 a.m. Kiddie Parade-Chamber Building Parking Lot
            12 p.m. Stars and Stripes Parade</description>
        <locLocation> Lake Bandshell Bloomington, MN</locLocation>

    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>8</locId>
        <locCity>Chanhassen</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The Chanhassen Fourth of July Celebration runs from July 2-4. For more information, see the city website.</description>
        <locLocation>1456 West 78th Street, Chanhassen, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>


    <locs>
        <locId>9</locId>
    <locCity>chaska</locCity>
    <locState>MN</locState>
    <description>The city of Chaska sponsored fireworks is at McKnight Park starting at dusk on July 4.
        The best viewing is from McKnight Park and the Home Depot parking lot.</description>
        <locLocation>Chaska, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>coonrapids</locCity>
        <locId>10</locId>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Also features a carnival, craft and craft show, live music and parade.</description>
        <locLocation>1008 Northdale Blvd. NW, Coon Rapids, Minn.</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs>
        <locId>11</locId>
    <locCity>cottage grove</locCity>
    <locState>MN</locState>
    <description>Celebrations kick off at 6 p.m. at Kingston Park with a family style picnic, games and food on Friday, July 4. Fireworks are scheduled for 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Cottage Grove, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>delano</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Come and join us for Minnesota's Oldest and Largest 4th of July Celebration
            in 2014 ; July 2, 3, 4, 5! Over the four days of events you can join tens of thousands as
            they enjoy a wide variety of food and drink, bingo, the nightly dances in the Entertainment Tent
            American Legion Baseball Tournament modified and slow pitch softball tournaments (tourney bracket PDFs now available!), a
            bean bag tournament, a kiddie parade, a 5K Race and the Delano Royalty Coronation, all surrounded by the fun and excitement of
            GoldStar Amusements carnival NOTE: While flooding has had minimal impact on the Central Park in Delano, organizers have made adjustments
            to parking areas to accommodate guests. Additional parking has been provided, and free parking and shuttle service from Delano High School
            will be provided.</description>
        <locLocation>Delano, MN</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>duluth</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10:10 p.m.
            Location: Bayfront Festival Park

            Admission: Free
            Details: Visit Bayfront Festival Park during the Independence Day Celebration! Duluthians and
            visitors alike will enjoy this FREE community celebration. Gates open at 4 p.m. and entertainment begins at 4:30 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation> Railroad St. and S. Fifth Ave. W., Duluth, Minn.</locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>Eagan</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>July 3 8211; 4, 2014. A star-spangled celebration is in store for you during
            Eagan's July 4 Funfest
            Celebration! Enjoy the Fourth of July Parade, Miss Eagan Funfest Ambassador Program, a carnival
            filled with thrilling rides and amusing games, live entertainment, and of course; a breathtaking fireworks
            display at 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Eagan, MN</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>edenprairie</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Round Lake Park

            Admission: Free
            Details: The Eden Prairie Hometown Celebration will be held from 7:30 a.m. to 11 p.m. July 4. The event will include music and food, and will culminate in a 10 p.m. fireworks show.
        </description>
        <locLocation>16691 Valley View Road, Eden Prairie, Minn</locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>edina</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Rosland Park
            Admission: Free
            Link: </description>
        <locLocation>4300 W. 66th St., Edina, Minn</locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>elkriver</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description><strong>Elk River</strong></description>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Lions Park
            Exact Location: 1104 Lions Park Drive, Elk River, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Family activities, food, music and more begin at 4 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation>1104 Lions Park Drive, Elk River, Minn</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>Minnetonka</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: Dusk
            Location: Commons Park
            Admission: Free
            Details: The concert is free, as is parking.
        </description>
        <locLocation>Minnetonka, Minn</locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>fairmont</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Ward and Sylvania Parks
            Exact Location: Ward: Albion Ave. and Webster Street; Sylvania: Beach Street and W. 3rd Street, Fairmont, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: One of greater Minnesota8217;s largest fireworks displays. Originating at Heritage Acres, the displays begin at dark and can be watched from Ward and Sylvania Parks.
        </description>
        <locLocation> W. 3rd Street, Fairmont, Minn</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>faribault</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>The annual 4th of July Fireworks Display will be held near South and North Alexander Parks. The show starts at 10:15 pm. In case of rain, the show will be held on July 5th. The show is sponsored by the Faribault Charitable Gambling Board.</description>
        <locLocation> faribault, Minn</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>forestlake</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Forest Lake, Minn.
            Exact Location: Forest Lake, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Parade at 10 a.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation> Forest Lake, Minn.</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>hamlake</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Ham Lake Residents will once again be able to celebrate the 4th of July close to home in Lions Park. The Don Hansen VFW Post will sponsor its annual celebration in honor of area veterans. Partying begins at 3 p.m. on the 4th with many fun activities! The Fireworks Display will begin at dusk!</description>
        <locLocation> Ham Lake, Minn.</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>hastings</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The annual F4th of July fireworks display is set for 10 p.m. Friday, July 4, at the Hastings Country Club. As it has for many years, the Vermillion State Bank is sponsoring the display.</description>
        <locLocation> Hastings, Minn.</locLocation> </locs>



    <locs> <locCity>hudson</locCity>
        <locState>WI</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/5/2014
            Time: 9-10 p.m.
            Location: Lakefront Park
            Exact Location: First St. &amp; Locust St., Hudson, Wis
            Admission: Free
        </description>

        <locLocation>Locust St Hudson, Wis </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>lakeville</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The Panorama of Progress, the Pan-O-Prog, is in its 48th year. The 10 day celebration, from July 4 until July 14, includes a car show, parade, sports tournaments and more. On July 4, there8217;s a parade, festival and firework show. The fireworks celebration will begin at 7 p.m. with a performance by the CASTAWAYS, followed by the fireworks display at 10 p.m. Fireworks can be seen from Lakeville North High School.</description>
        <locLocation>Lakeville, MN </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>mankato</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Riverfront Park
            Exact Location: Riverfront Drive and Rock Street, Mankato, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: The annual Red Hot &amp; Boom celebration features live music, live radio broadcast and fireworks. The celebration kicks off at 7 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation>Riverfront Drive Mankato, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>maplegrove</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>During Maple Grove Days, July 10-14, the city will feature parades, games, food, competitions, street dances and much more at the Maple Grove Community Center. Fireworks will be on July 13 at dusk.</description>
        <locLocation>maplegrove, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>maplewood</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The 4th of July celebration, Light It Up Maplewood, starts at 4 p.m. at Hazelwood Park, 1663 County Road C East. The event is free with live entertainment starting at 6:30 p.m. The event ends with the annual fireworks show.</description>
        <locLocation>maplewood, MN </locLocation> </locs>



    <locs> <locCity>Marine</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Help us celebrate Marine's Annual 4th of July festivities!
            Our fantastic fireworks spectacular will be Thursday, July 3rd in downtown Marine at dusk.</description>
        <locLocation>Marine, MN </locLocation> </locs>



    <locs> <locCity>Mendota Heights</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The Mendakota Country Club will be having July 4th fireworks for their members, but people can view the fireworks at nearby parking lots. The fireworks will be happening at 10 p.m. on July 4th at the Mendakota Country Club located at 2075 Mendakota Drive, Mendota Heights, Minn.</description>
        <locLocation>Mendota, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>moorhead</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description><span style="text-decoration:underline;">University of Minnesota Moorhead</span>
            6:30 p.m. Concessions at Nemzek Hall &amp; Stadium
            7:00 p.m. Inflatable games (until 9:30 p.m.)
            7:30 p.m. Kids8217; Decorated Bike Parade, Sponsored by Moorhead Public Service
            7:30 p.m. Lake Agassiz Concert Band
            8:30 p.m. Front Fenders
            10:30 p.m. Fireworks, Sponsored by American Crystal Sugar
        </description>
        <locLocation>Moorhead, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>New Prague</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>New Prague will have fireworks at 10:10 p.m. Thursday, July 3 east of the New Prague Middle School. This year8217;s fireworks is sponsored by NPCL Mutual Insurance Company. Bring a non-perishable food item to donate to the Peace Center Food Drive.</description>
        <locLocation>New Prague, MN </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>northfield</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Northfield Middle School ground
            Exact Location: 220 Division St. S.
        </description>
        <locLocation>220 Division St. S Northfield, MN </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>Oakdale</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 4 p.m. 8212; vendors open
            Location: Richard Walton Park
            Exact Location: 1584 Hadley Ave N, Oakdale, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Oakdale8217;s Fourth of July celebration will feature vendors and live music in addition to fireworks. Most vendors will open at 4 p.m., and the Rockin8217; Hollywoods are set to play at the bandshell from 7 8211; 10 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation>1584 Hadley Ave N, Oakdale, Minn </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>Owatonna</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Fireworks will be held at 10 p.m. at the Steele County Fairgrounds, located at 1525 S. Cedar Ave.</description>
        <locLocation>Owatona, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>parkrapids</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>The city of Park Rapids will celebrate the 4th of July with a 5K run/walk at 9 a.m. Following the race, there will be a baking contest and auction. Entry is $5 per pie. All pies will be auctioned at 3:30 p.m. The annual 4th of July parade will begin on Main Street at 5 p.m. Following the parade the Park Rapids Area Community band will perform at 7:30 p.m., finishing with a fireworks display over Fish Hook River and Heartland Park.</description>
        <locLocation>Park Rapids, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>plymouth</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Date: 7/1/2014
            Time: 10:15 p.m.
            Location: Hilde Performance Center
            Exact Location: 3450 Plymouth Blvd, Plymouth, MN
            Admission: Free
            Details: Tuesday, July 1, is their only summer day with fireworks
        </description>
        <locLocation>3450 Plymouth Blvd, Plymouth, MN</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>priorlake</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Mystic Lake Hotel and Casino
            Exact Location: 2400 Mystic Lake Blvd., Prior Lake, MN
            Admission: Free
            Details: Live bands and food trucks. Festivities start at 5 p.m. Fireworks at 10 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation>2400 Mystic Lake Blvd., Prior Lake, MN </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>richfield</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Veteran8217;s Memorial Park
            Exact Location: Veteran's Memorial Park, 64th Street and Portland Avenue S., Richfield, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Festivities begin on July 2 and run through July 5.
        </description>
        <locLocation>Veteran's Memorial Park, Richfield, Minn. </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>robbinsdale</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/10/2014 7/13/2014
            Location: Robbinsdale, Minn.
            Exact Location: Event dependent.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Festivities begin on July 10 and run through July 13.
        </description>
        <locLocation> Robbinsdale, Minn</locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>rochester</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>On July 4, Riverside Concerts presents Chuck Blattner directing the Rochester Concert Band
            performing a concert in tribute to the anniversary of our country8217;s independence at the Silver Lake
            Park soccer field. The concert is FREE to the public and will precede the fireworks display.
            Fireworks start at 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Rochester, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>roseville</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 1:30-10:30 p.m.
            Location: Central Park-Lexington East
            Exact Location: 2540 Lexington Ave., Roseville, MN
            Admission: Free
            Details: Music and vendors throughout the afternoon and evening, fireworks at dusk.
        </description>
        <locLocation>2540 Lexington Ave, Roseville, MN</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>shakopee</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description><strong>Shakopee</strong></description>
        <description>Valleyfair, Shakopee: Fireworks at 9:50 p.m. on July 4 near Planet Snoopy Plaza. Also, all active and retired military personnel get free admission on July 3 8211; July 6.</description>
        <locLocation>Valleyfair Shakopee, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>shoreview</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>Slice of Shoreview Days will be from July 23-27 at Island Lake County Park.
            Most of the events will take place across the weekend from July 25-27. For more information,
            here. Some of the highlights include:
            Friday, July 26
            3:30 p.m. Helicopter Rides
            4:30 p.m. Amateur Talent Show winners
            5 p.m. Carnival
            10 p.m. Fireworks
            Saturday, July 27
            10 a.m. Parade, carnival
            Noon Bungee Trampoline &amp; Climbing Wall
            10 p.m. Fireworks
            Sunday, July 28
            8 a.m. Pancake Breakfast
            11 a.m. Carnival
            Noon Car and motorcycle show</description>
        <locLocation>Shoreview, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>St.Cloud</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Hester Park/Wilson Park
            Admission: Free
            Details: St. Cloud is proud to present the 67th annual July 4 Fireworks display along the banks of the Mississippi River in the heart of beautiful St. Cloud, Minne. Synchronized to a special soundtrack, this years fireworks show promises to cap a sensational day of fun and relaxation with one of the largest fireworks displays anywhere in Minnesota on July 4!
        </description>
        <locLocation>Wilson Park St.Cloud, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>St Joseph</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>

        <description>4th Of July Festival 2014
            Thursday, July 3
            5:50 p.m. 8212; Festival Opening Prayer
            6 p.m. 8212; Free 8220;Joetown Rocks8221; Concert* Sponsored by All Saints Academy,
            Leighton Broadcasting, Pam’s Auto, Sentry Bank, Sunset Manufacturing, and Tiremaxx Service.
            6 p.m. 8212; KJ And The Graduates
            6:45 p.m. 8212; Jeremiah James Korfe
            8 p.m. 8212; 8220;Rumours and Dreams – A Fleetwood Mac Tribute8221; by Pamela McNeill, Mary Jane Alm, and Jeff Engholm
            10:15 p.m. 8212; Fireworks Sponsored by Bernicks
            10:30 p.m. 8212; Shalo Lee Band
            Friday, July 4
            8 a.m. 8212; Mass
            10 a.m. 8212; Parade Sponsored by the Lions Club
            11 a.m. 8212; Bingo, Games, Food, Refreshments (on parish grounds)
            11:30 a.m. 8212; Live Music by 8220;Smok8217;N Guns Band8221;
            2 p.m. 8212; Quilt Auction
            3:30 p.m. 8212; Raffle Drawing</description>
        <locLocation>St Joseph, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>St Louis Park</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Aquila Park
            Exact Location: 3110 Xylon Ave. S., St. Louis Park, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Concessions, vendors and live music from 7 p.m. to 9:30 p.m. Rain date: July 5 (Weather line is 952-924-2567)
        </description>
        <locLocation>3110 Xylon Ave. S., St. Louis Park, Minn</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>St Michael</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>While it may not have it8217;s own fireworks display, residents of St. Michael are invited to view Elk River8217;s
            4th of July fireworks just a few miles away at Lions Park.
            Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 10 p.m.
            Location: Lions Park
            Exact Location: 1104 Lions Park Drive, Elk River, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Family activities, food, music and more begin at 4 p.m.
        </description>
        <locLocation>1104 Lions Park Drive, Elk River, Minn</locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>stewartville</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Summerfest 2014
            Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 6 p.m. parade, fireworks at dusk
            Location: Florence Park
            Exact Location: Lakeshore Drive NW and 2nd Street NW, Stewartville, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Summerfest 2014 begins on Thursday, July 3 with a street dance at 6 p.m. Friday8217;s events will
            include a fun run, arts in the park, a parade and the fireworks at dusk.
        </description>
        <locLocation>Lakeshore Drive NW Stewartville, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>stillwater</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>A day of live music and entertainment in downtown
            Stillwater is followed by fireworks over the St. Croix at dusk.
            Fourth of July fireworks/concert &amp; fun: Come for an old-fashioned J
            uly Fourth celebration in Lowell Park on the St. Croix River. Fireworks start at
            10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Stillwater, MN </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>waconia</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Waconia will have their Fantastic Fireworks Show on July 4 at dusk on the eastern edge of Lake Waconia Regional Park. Viewing is best from a boat on Lake Waconia, Lola8217;s Lakehouse, Lake Waconia Regional Park and Laketown Parkway. Rain Date is July 5.</description>
        <locLocation>Waconia, MN </locLocation> </locs>

    <locs> <locCity>whitebearlake</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 8 p.m. Music starts, 10 p.m. Fireworks.
            Location: West Park and Memorial Beach
            Exact Location: 4980 Lake Ave N, White Bear Lake, Minn.
            Admission: Free
            Details: Part of Manitou days, this display features a spectacular fireworks show set to music over the lake. Earlier in the day, enjoy food, arts &amp; crafts, classic car show, kids activities &amp; more.
        </description>
        <locLocation>4980 Lake Ave N, White Bear Lake, Minn </locLocation> </locs>


    <locs> <locCity>Woodbury</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Date: 7/4/2014
            Time: 7 p.m. 8211; festivities begin
            Location: Bielenberg Sports Center
            Exact Location: 4125 Radio Dr, Woodbury, Minn.</description>
        <locLocation>4125 Radio Dr, Woodbury, Minn</locLocation> </locs>






</locations>
