<?xml version="1.0"?>
<locations>
    <locs>
        <locId>1</locId>
        <locCity>Minneapolis</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Red, White and BOOM celebrates Independence Day with music, entertainment and family fun on the Minneapolis Riverfront on July 3 and 4. Fireworks are at 10 p.m. on July 4. (NOTE: Powderhorn Park, Minneapolis will still host a Fourth of July celebration — with live music, children’s activities, and local food vendors — but will NOT feature a fireworks display this year.)</description>
        <locLocation>221 SE Main St Minneapolis, MN </locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>2</locId>
        <locCity>Albert Lea</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>On July 3, come see the largest parade in Southern Minnesota at 6 p.m. The parade has over 100 units and will travel Bridge and Fountain Streets.
            July 4 is one of the largest fireworks display in Southern Minnesota and Northern Iowa. Watch the beautiful reflection off of Fountain Lake at 10 p.m..
            Prior to the fireworks, the 4th Of July celebration will include:
            Community Band concert at 8 p.m. at the Gazebo.
            Bayside Ski Show at 2 p.m. at Edgewater Park.
            Car Show from 4 – 7 p.m. on N. Broadway.</description>
        <locLocation>Albert Lea, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>3</locId>
        <locCity>Alexandria</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Enjoy a free concert on the courthouse lawn beginning at 7 p.m. Friday, July 4. The concert is presented by the Red Willow Arts Coalition and will have a patriotic theme.
            Star Storm 2014 is a music and fireworks spectacular that is presented each year on the grounds of Arrowwood Resort. Tune your radio to KX92 – 92.3 FM to hear a patriotic sound track to the
            largest fireworks show in West Central Minnesota. It’s FREE and open to the public. Rainbow Rider shuttles will be running from the stables beginning at 7 p.m., fireworks begin at 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Alexandria, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>4</locId>
        <locCity>Andover</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description> July 3rd — Fireworks at AHS, at dusk
            July 4th — Family Fun in The Park:
            Pancake Breakfast — 8 – 11 am
            Jazz Band — 8 – 10 am
            Horribles Parade line-up — 9 am
            Horribles Parade — 9:30 am
            Games in The Park — 10 – 11:30 am
            Middlesex Concert Band — 10:30 – noon</description>
        <locLocation>Andover, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>5</locId>
        <locCity>Blaine</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description> What’s an Independence Day celebration
            without fireworks? Have your cameras ready and be
            prepared to be amazed by a fireworks display like no
            other Firework Extravaganza on July 4th at 10 p.m. at
            the National Sports Center</description>
        <locLocation>1700 150th Ave NE Blaine, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>6</locId>
        <locCity>Bloomington</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Summer Fete on July 3 celebrates Independence Day with a kid’s carnival, entertainment and live music.
            Fireworks will begin around 10 p.m. at Normandale Lake Bandshell.</description>
        <locLocation> Lake Bandshell Bloomington, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>7</locId>
        <locCity>Brainard</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>July 3rd
            5 p.m. Trampoline Bungee jumps, dunk tanks and food vendors
            5 – 8 p.m. Petting Zoo by Safari North Wildlife Park
            8 – 10 p.m. Music performance by Taylor Reed
            Fireworks, presented by Zambelli Fireworks, begin after dusk at the International-High School Ball Fields.
            July 4
            9 a.m.-4 p.m. Flea Market, Craft Fair and Food Vendors – Trailside Park
            10 a.m. Money in the Haystack-Trailside Park
            10:30 a.m. Kiddie Parade Registration-Chamber Building Parking Lot
            11 a.m. Kiddie Parade-Chamber Building Parking Lot
            12 p.m. Stars and Stripes Parade</description>
        <locLocation> Lake Bandshell Bloomington, MN</locLocation>

    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>8</locId>
        <locCity>Chanhassen</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>The Chanhassen Fourth of July Celebration runs from July 2-4. For more information, see the city website.</description>
        <locLocation>1456 West 78th Street, Chanhassen, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>



</locations>
