<?xml version="1.0"?>
<locations>
    <locs>
        <locId>1</locId>
        <locCity>Minneapolis</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Red, White and BOOM celebrates Independence Day with music, entertainment and family fun on the Minneapolis Riverfront on July 3 and 4. Fireworks are at 10 p.m. on July 4. (NOTE: Powderhorn Park, Minneapolis will still host a Fourth of July celebration — with live music, children’s activities, and local food vendors — but will NOT feature a fireworks display this year.)</description>
        <locLocation>221 SE Main St Minneapolis, MN </locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>2</locId>
        <locCity>Albert Lea</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>On July 3, come see the largest parade in Southern Minnesota at 6 p.m. The parade has over 100 units and will travel Bridge and Fountain Streets.
            July 4 is one of the largest fireworks display in Southern Minnesota and Northern Iowa. Watch the beautiful reflection off of Fountain Lake at 10 p.m..
            Prior to the fireworks, the 4th Of July celebration will include:
            Community Band concert at 8 p.m. at the Gazebo.
            Bayside Ski Show at 2 p.m. at Edgewater Park.
            Car Show from 4 – 7 p.m. on N. Broadway.</description>
        <locLocation>350</locLocation>
    </locs>
    <locs>
        <locId>3</locId>
        <locCity>Alexandria</locCity>
        <locState>MN</locState>
        <description>Enjoy a free concert on the courthouse lawn beginning at 7 p.m. Friday, July 4. The concert is presented by the Red Willow Arts Coalition and will have a patriotic theme.
            Star Storm 2014 is a music and fireworks spectacular that is presented each year on the grounds of Arrowwood Resort. Tune your radio to KX92 – 92.3 FM to hear a patriotic sound track to the
            largest fireworks show in West Central Minnesota. It’s FREE and open to the public. Rainbow Rider shuttles will be running from the stables beginning at 7 p.m., fireworks begin at 10 p.m.</description>
        <locLocation>Alexandria, MN</locLocation>
    </locs>

</locations>
